Sincro: wyxchari
- 都搞定了  - 很好
- All set.   - Good.
你不是想知道变色龙观光游的秘密吗？
You wanted to know the secret of Chameleon Tours.
好了，督察...
Well Inspector,
你自己看！
see for yourself!
- 博士！  - 他死了！
- Doctor!   - He's dead!
你跟我来
You're coming with me.
我不会离开他
I'll not leave him.
你有五秒钟改变主义
You have five seconds to change your mind.
除非你先杀了我
You'll have to kill me then.
我说了五秒
I said five seconds.
五，四，三...
Five, four, three...
SAMANTHA!​
SAMANTHA!
我想问这飞机往哪儿开，估计问也白问
I suppose there's no use my asking
where this plane's going to?
你很快就能知道了
You will know soon enough.
三号飞机呼叫基地
This is Plane Number Three to Base.
告诉总管我已经按他吩咐给他找了一个替身
Inform the Director that I have
an original for him as ordered.
正在运送过来
I am delivering him now,
然后会立刻返回盖特威克机场
and will return immediately to Gatwick Airport.
Jamie？你没事吧
Jamie? Are you all right?
没事。他们..没有伤到你吧，有吗？
Aye. Th... They've not harmed you, have they?
没有，但我动不了
No - but I can't move.
博士？
Doctor?
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
发生什么了？我...我动不了了
What's happening? I... I can't move.
那是什么？
What's that?
我...我不知道，是一束光
I... I don't know. It's a beam of light.
是。博士，它...在朝我们移动！
Aye. Doctor, it... it's moving towards us!
这对于将要发生在我们身上的事来说，只是一道小小的开胃菜
That's just a small fore-taste
of what'll happen to us //
要是我们还不赶紧挪开的话
if we don't move and quickly.
- 但我动不了，博士！  - 我也动不了
- But I can't move, Doctor!  - Neither can I.
等一下，我可以移动一只胳膊
Wait a minute. I can move one arm.
但我移动不了！
But I can't move away!
噢博士！你不能想什么办法停掉它吗？
Oh Doctor! Can't you do anything to stop it?
没办法
No.
等等，有一个
Wait. One thing.
虽然机会不大，但也许能成功
It's a long chance but it just might work.
你包里有镜子吗?
Have you got a mirror in that bag?
- 有  - 我看看
- Yes.   - Let's see.
嗯，这应该可以。把它给我
Yes, that'll do. Hand it to me.
- 给不了  - 我没法移动我的手
- I can't.  - I can't move my hand.
Jamie，你能拿到吗？
Jamie, can you take it?
- 你拿到了吗？  - 还没，小心！
- Have you got it?   - No, careful!
- 接着！ - 接到了！
- Take it!   - Got it!
现在，看看你能否把它对准那个射线枪
Right now, see if you can point it at that laser gun.
- 墙上的那个东西 - 我试试，博士。不过为啥？
- That thing on the wall.
- I'll try, Doctor. But why?
如果你能把光反射回去，我们就有机会了
If you can reflect the light back,
we've got a chance.
你不能拿什么东西撑住它吗
Can't you prop it up on something?
不，不行...我，我用手拿着吧
No, it won't work.
I'll... I'll have to hold it.//
但是你...你的手！
But your...your hand!//
这个风险我不得不担
It's a risk I'll have to take.
快 Jamie！赶紧！
Quick Jamie! Now!
噢，干得好！
Oh, well done!
为什么...我动不了！
Why... I can move!
我...我觉得可能...
I... I wonder if...
你觉得 Ben 和 Polly 是不是也遭遇了这个，博士？
Do you think that's what happened
to Ben and Polly, Doctor?
- 不是  - 你肯定吗？
- No.   - Are you sure?
我觉得他们拿他俩有别的用途
I think they were needed for some purpose.
- 而我们没有？  - 显然我们对他们太危险了
- And we weren't.
- We were obviously too dangerous for them.
竟然想干这样的事情，在光天化日之下！
But to try and do something like this,
in broad daylight!
是啊。这只可能意味着一件事情，恐怕
Yes. That means only one thing, I'm afraid.
他们的计划快要完成了
Their plans are almost complete.
我们必须赶紧行动，否则别想就 Polly 和 Ben 了
We'll have to act fast
if we're going to save Polly and Ben.
还有 Brian，你是不是已经忘记他了
And Brian, or have you forgotten about him.
没，我没有忘记他，Sam
No, I've not forgotten him Sam,
但如果我的猜测没错的话，他们都在同一个地方
but if my guess is right,
they're all in the same place.
- 在什么地方？  - 我不知道
- And where's that?  - I don't know.
等等！急救站！
Wait! The first aid post!
我们在那个监视器里面看到了一个急救站
We saw a first aid post on that monitor.
我们必须找到它
We must find it.
快点，你没打算在这里坐一整天吧，有吗？
Come on, you're not going to
sit there all day are you?
等一下，我们不能全都涌去急救站
Just a minute. We can't all
go down to the Medical Unit.
好吧，我能干点什么？
All right. What can I do?
那个想杀我们的男人，你有没有看清楚？
Did you get a good look
at the man who tried to kill us?
应该有吧，我都用脖子勒住他脖子了
I'll say. I had my arms around his neck.
去变色龙的柜台，看看能否看到他进出
Go down to the Chameleon Kiosk
and see if he comes in or out.
- 好  - 但是小心点，别让他看见你
- Right!
- But be careful. Don't let him see you.
我小心点？你俩自己小心点吧，我肯定没事
Me be careful!? You two watch out
for yourselves! I'll be OK!
她很有勇气，那个小姑娘，博士
She's got a lot of courage,
that wee lass, Doctor.
是，我只是期望她不要太冒险了
Yes. I just hope she doesn't
try to be too adventurous.
你是谁？
Who are you?
Steven Christopher Jenkins​
Steven Christopher Jenkins
你住在哪里？
Where do you live?
跟我父母一起住在温布尔顿
With my parents in Wimbledon.
职业呢？
Employment?
我是个移民局官员，在盖特威克机场工作
I'm an Immigration Officer, at Gatwick Airport.
过来，慢点。你很快就没事了
Come along, easy. You'll be all right.
过来，慢点
Now come along, take it easy.
我们马上会让你安然无恙
We'll have you as right as rain in a minute.
现在在这里坐下FIXME，就这里
Now just get you down here. There we are.
- 很好  - 我怎么样，博士？
- Splendid.   - How am I doing, Doctor?
很好，但不要装过头了
Very well but don't over do it.
是了，就是这个房间。我们在监视器上看到的
Yes, this is the room.
We see... saw on the TV monitor.
如果这些药片没作用，再过来找我
If the tablets do not help, come and see me again.
- 他这是怎么了？  - 是一种罕见的热带疾病
- What's the matter with him?
- It's a rare tropical disease,
护士，我是他的医生
Nurse. I'm his doctor.
如果他...他不能很快恢复，我们就...
If he... if he doesn't rally soon we shall err... //
我们就得给他用点梭玛林
we shall have to use somnalin.
- 梭玛林？  - 是的...对，梭玛林
- Somnalin?  - Yes... yes, somnalin
所以我得找个地方让他躺下
So l have to get him somewhere to lie down.
哦对了，这里应该很合适
Oh yes, this will do nicely.
恐怕..你不能进里面去
I... I'm afraid you can't go there.
为什么不能？这只是个X光室，是吧？
Why not? It's just an X-ray room, isn't it?//
屏风后面不是张躺椅吗？
Isn't that a couch behind the screen.
抱歉，医生，你不能把你的病人带进去
I'm sorry, Doctor.
You can't take your patient in there.
- 你拒绝给我的病患帮助？  - 不，不是这样的
- You refuse to help my patient?
- Oh, it's not that.
- 我有一个病人要来拍X光片  - 哦，我明白了
- I have someone coming for an X-ray.  - Oh I see.
那你怎么不一开始就告诉我呢？
Well why didn't you tell me in the first place.
来把你扶出去
Let's get you out of here.
这个博士对我们的计划是个威胁
That Doctor is a menace to our plans.
那我们必须杀了他
Then we must kill him.
我试过了，他肯定是又逃掉了
I tried. He must have escaped.
- 他们从我这里逃不了  - 不，等等
- They won't escape me.  - No, wait.
这一次，让他们来找我
This time, let them to come to us.
我一直在联系他，警司，但他一直没接
I've been paging him, Superintendent,
but he hasn't responded.
是，很好，先生。我会继续尝试
Yes, very well sir. I'll keep on trying.
接线员。我订了一个到雅典的电话，现在怎样了
Operator. Look, I booked a call through
to Athens, now what happened?
对，好吧。我在电话旁边等着
Yes, very well, I'll stay near the phone.
这都是怎么回事？
What's all this about?
- 噢博士，你见到 Crossland 督察了吗？  - 没有，怎么了？
- Oh Doctor, have you seen Inspector Crossland?
- Well no. Why?
哦，苏格兰场在找他，但我们在哪里都找不到
Well, Scotland Yard are looking for him
and we can't find him anywhere.
还有，Briggs 小姐想找你
Also, your Miss Briggs wants to see you.
但我跟她说了...她现在在哪儿？
But I told her to... Where is she now?
她说要去什么变色龙柜台
Well she said something about
going to the Chameleon Kiosk.
你去看看情况，Jamie
Go down and join her, Jamie.
她这个年轻女人很有主见
She's a very strong headed young woman.
- 确保她不会碰到什么麻烦  - 我会看着她的，博士
- See she doesn't come to any trouble.
- I'll keep an eye on her, Doctor.
总指挥，督察说过他要去哪儿了吗？
Commandant, did the Inspector say
where he was going?
唔，他说他要去找变色龙观光游问问情况
Hmm, oh he said he was going to
make some enquires about Chameleon Tours.
但他现在不见了？
And now he's disappeared?
- 你这结论下得也太快了吧？  - 我没觉得
- Aren't you rather jumping to conclusions?
- I don't think so.
我的两个朋友牵涉进变色龙观光游，他俩都不见了
My two friends became involved with Chameleon Tours,
and they've both disappeared.
你知道我的猜测是什么
However, you know what I think has happened.
是的，你也知道我对你那荒谬的想法是怎么看的
Yes, and you know what I think
about your ridiculous theory.
外太空来的人，真的是
People from outer space, indeed.
你这是怎么了
Something the matter with you?
总指挥，我发现是怎么回事了
Commandant, I've found out what's been happening.
好，朝着正确的方向迈近了一步
Well, that's a step in the right direction.
我的意思是，我擅做主张，给所有机场打了电话
Wh... what I mean is, I took the liberty
of phoning all the airports
所以变色龙飞去的地方
that ah... err... Chameleon Tours fly to.
最后打的是雅典
The last on my list was Athens.
你就没意识到到雅典的电话费...
Don't you realise the expense of phoning Ath...
是的我知道，我很抱歉
Yes, I know, I'm sorry.
但是我发现了，他们从来没有运送任何乘客
But what I found out is -
they never deliver any passengers.
你说的什么意思？从来没有运送任何乘客？
What do you mean? Never deliver any passengers...
绝对是真的，先生。他们说的全都一样
It's absolutely true, sir.
They all say the same thing.
杜布罗夫尼克，雅典，罗马
Dubrovnik, Athens, Rome.
他们说年轻乘客搭上飞机去其它地方，但是...
They say they pick up young passengers
to take them off to other places but...
没有一个人到达任何地方！
none of them ever arrive anywhere!
要是这样的话，他们肯定把这些人运到了某个秘密的机场
Well in that case, they must be flying
these young people to some secret airfield.
- 但是为什么呢？ - 你仍然还是地球人的思维
- But why?
- You're still thinking in Earth terms.
我还就打算坚持这种思维
And I intend to go on doing so.
- 变色龙的飞行员是谁？  - Blade 机长
- What was the name of that Chameleon Pilot?
- Captain Blade.
- 飞机预计什么时候回来  - 还有半个小时，先生
- And what time is the plane due back?
- About half an hour, sir.
好，等这次掉头了，我们派人跟踪他们
Right. After the turn-round
we'll have it followed this time.
我能跟你说句话吗，亲爱的？
Could I have a word with you, my dear?
给我接皇家空军曼斯顿站
Get me the RAF Station Manston.
我怀疑急救中心跟这一切有联系
I suspect that the Medical Centre
is connected with all this.
- 急救中心..得了  - 请不要跟他一样
- Medical Cen... Oh come on...
- Now please don't get like him.
是的，这里绝对有联系
Oh yes, there is definitely a connection,
现在，我打算进里面去，看一圈
now, I would like to get in there
and have a look round.
任何人都可以进去啊
But anyone can go in there.
但我期望能先把那个护士引开
But I would like to get that nurse
out of the way first...
你觉得你能帮我搞定吗？
Do you think that you can manage it for me?
你会发现这是没问题的
You'll find that in order.
他说你会做些傻事
He said you'd do something silly.
是吗？他还说什么了？
Oh yeah, what else did he say?
- 他说你很有主见  - 很好，你可以告诉博士
- He said you were headstrong.
- Oh great. Look, you can tell the Doctor
他不可能说服我放弃这个，你也不能
he's not going to talk me out of this one,
and neither are you.
我要登上变色龙的下一次航班，还有半小时起飞
I'm going on the next Chameleon flight,
that leaves in half an hour.
你还没有明白吗，这是我们能查到线索的唯一途径
Oh look don't you see, it's the only way
we can find out anything.
哦，别担心，我会回来告诉把全部经过都告诉你的
Oh, don't worry. I'll come back
and tell you all about it.
- 那你得回得来  - 哦，只是去一趟罗马罢了
- If you do come back.
- Oh, it's only going to Rome.
凭什么你确信你能在罗马找到你弟弟？
And what makes you so sure
you'll find your brother in Rome?
哦，我不知道。但那是他本来应该抵达的地方
Oh, I don't know. But that's where
he was supposed to be going.
至少我可以做点什么
At least I'll be doing something. //
是。但你没有意识到这有多危险
Aye, but do you not realise
how dangerous it is.
你可能是害怕了，我可没有
Look if you're scared, I'm certainly not.
- 要是博士在这里就好了  - 噢
- I wish the Doctor were here.
- Oh.
嘿，也许我可以和你一起去
Hey, maybe I could go with you.
嘿，这还差不多。
Hey, now you're talking.
你觉得你买得机票吗？
Do you think you can you raise the lolly?
- 机票？  - 费用，钱
- The lolly?  - The brass, the money.
会花费你28块钱，或者说英镑
Look it will cost you twenty-eight
quid - pounds to you.
哦，那是好大一笔钱。我从来没有这么多钱
Oh but that's a fortune.
I've never seen that much money in my life.
- 我估计..我不能可以替你去吗？ - 不行
- I suppose I... I couldn't take your place?
- No!
博士说这可不是一个小姑娘能干的事情
The Doctor said it was er...
no job for a wee lassie...
- 一个小姑娘！你可以告诉博士... - 说再见吧
- A wee lassie! You can tell the Doctor...
- I say goodbye.
嘿，小子！我可以照顾好自己，知道吧
Hey, kid! I can take care of myself, you know.
我只是不太放心
I just wanted to make sure.
唔，所以你可以安排人跟踪？
Hmm. So you can arrange to have it followed?
好，我会搞明白的
Good. Oh I'll find out.//
变色龙的下一趟航班什么时候？
What time's the next Chameleon flight?
15:30飞罗马，先生
1530hrs to Rome, sir.
15:30 往南飞
1530hrs heading South.
好，等他们请求起飞的时候我会通知你
Right. And I'll let you know
when they request permission to start up.
再见老伙计，很是感谢
Cheerio old man and many thanks.
好了，都安排妥了
Well, that's settled that.
变色龙的下一趟航班就会有皇家空军跟在它后面了
The next Chameleon flight
will have an RAF fighter on its tail.
老天，Jean，Jean！
Good grief. Jean. Jean!
这姑娘怎么了？找急救中心
What's the matter with the girl?
Get me the Medical Centre.
你的助手不能自己到这里来吗，总指挥？
Isn't it possible for your assistant
to come down here, Commandant.
但我不能离开这里啊
But I'm not supposed to leave here.
好吧，先生，既然你坚持的话
All right sir, if you insist.
我要下班了
I'm just going off duty,
但这位先生会很高兴继续照顾你
but err this gentleman
will be pleased to attend to you.
- 你现在觉得怎样  - 不太好
- How do you feel now?  - Not too good.
我就不明白了，她从来没有这样过
I can't understand it.
She's never done this on me before.
谢谢你护士，我现在觉得好多了
Thank you Nurse. I feel much better now.
那就应该没有什么大事
Well there couldn't be much wrong then.
你吃过午饭了吗？
Have you had any lunch?
没，我今天一直很忙，连早饭都还没有吃
No I've been so busy today,
I haven't even had any breakfast.
那怪不得你会不舒服了
Then no wonder you didn't feel well.
真的总指挥，你必须得让你的下属有时间按时吃饭
Really Commandant. You must see that
your staff have time for regular meals.
我从没阻止过她吃午饭！
I've never stopped her having her lunch!
我确信，总指挥，但这种事总还是会发生
I'm sure, Commandant.
But it has been known to happen.
- 来看看这儿  - 做得很好！
- Now look here.   - Very well done!
- 我有没有给你足够时间  - 很多时间
- Did I give you enough time? - Ample time.
这都是怎么回事？你完全就没病，对不？
What is all this?
You weren't ill at all, were you?
没事了，总指挥，她是按我的指示在演戏
It's all right, Commandant.
She was acting on my instructions.
- 按你的指示？ - 是。你对这些东西怎么看
- On your instructions?
- Yes. What do you think of these?
这些是什么？
Now, what are these?
我猜这里有人能告诉我们
I think there's somebody here who can tell us.
打扰了
Excuse me.
一直坐在这里的那个家伙哪里去了？
Where's the chap who usually sits there?
哦他很可能是下班了
Well he's probably off duty.
如果是这样的话，他应该过几个小时就会回来上班了
In that case, he'll be back on shift
in a couple of hours.
我知道了。好吧，看来得等了
I see. Oh well, these'll have to wait.
变色龙青年观光游通知您//
Chameleon Youth Tours announce the departure
飞往罗马的419航班即将起飞
of their flight number Four-One-Nine to Rome.
请所有旅客在候机室集合
Will all passengers please
assemble in the departure lounge.
不要忘了您的明信片
Don't forget your postcards.
把它们交给我，我们将会帮你们寄出去...
Give them back to me
and we'll post them for you when...
你找到你的机票了吗？
Have you found your ticket yet?
我不知道，好像是在某个地方弄丢了
I don't know. I seem to have lost it somewhere.
但你认得我的，对吧，我从你这里买的票
But you remember me, don't you?
I bought it off you.
又太多人了...名字是什么？
There are so many people...
what was the name?
呃，Samantha Briggs
Err, Samantha Briggs.//
噢，机票上写的是 S. Briggs
Oh, it had S. Briggs on the ticket.
S. Briggs has already checked in.
S. Briggs 已经检票进去了
哦不。到底是谁...
Oh no. Well, who the heck...
你记得那姑娘长什么样吗？
Look, can you remember what she looked like?
姑娘？我好像记得拿票的是个小伙子
She? I seem to remember a boy with that ticket.
Jamie! 他偷走了票。我说，你们必须要拦住他！
Jamie! He's pinched it.
Look you have to stop him!
我没法拦住飞机
I can't hold up the flight.
但是听着...
But look...
我很抱歉，我帮不了你什么了
I'm sorry, there's nothing more
I can do for you.
你好
Hello.
好了，没事了，你真是太好了
Yes, all right. That's very kind of you.
你很幸运，你的票找到了
You're very fortunate.
Your ticket's just been found.
- 噢好，谁捡到了？ - 恐怕我们不能告诉你
- Oh good. Well who got it?
- We can't tell you that I'm afraid.
但我们经理想要见你，那就在那边
but our manager would like to see you.
He's just through there.
好，拜
Oh right, ta.
现在，谁把明信片准备好了？
Now, who's got their postcards ready?
- 呃，是你想见我？ - 对，真的
- Er, you wanted to see me?  - Yes, indeed.
你再也逃不了了！
You won't escape again!
变色龙419，准许出港
Chameleon Four-One-Nine. Clearance correct.
变色龙419，准许滑行
Chameleon Four-One-Nine. Taxi Clearance?
变色龙419，沿南滑行道滑行，
Chameleon Four-One-Nine.
Taxi following southern taxiway
- 准备离开27号跑道  - 收到
- for departure runway two-seven. - Roger.
这一次他们就有皇家空军跟在屁股后面了！
Well this time they'll have the RAF on their tail!
现在这些战斗机可以到达多高，总指挥？
How high can fighters go these days, Commandant?
- 哦，十英里以上  - 好逊
- Oh, ten miles plus. - How futile.
- 曼斯顿皇家空军基地，先生  - 哦好
- RAF Manston, sir.  - Oh, good.
你好，老小子。变色龙的罗马航班刚刚起飞
Hello, old boy.
The Chameleon Rome flight's just taken off.
他们在琥珀一号上，飞行高度210
They're on Amber One,
at flight level two-one-zero.
好，祝好
Right. Good man.
你们可以解开安全带了，谢谢
You can unfasten your seat belts now. Thank you.
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
- 啊，我会没事的  - 好
- Oh aye, I'll be all right. - Good.
他们正要跨越50英里的标记点
That's the fifty-mile mark they're passing now.
通常你们在这个距离看不到他们吧
Normally you don't plot them at this range?
看不到，有太多飞机需要控制了
No, there's too much traffic to control.
一旦他们起飞，进入空中走廊，就跟我们没关系了
Once they're up and away on their air corridor,
we're finished with them.
你好，盖特威克机场。这里是皇家空军241
Hello, Gatwick Airport. This is RAF Two-Four-One.//
你们可以听到吗？
How do you read me?
盖特威克机场呼叫RAF-241，我们可以清晰地听到
Gatwick Airport to RAF Two-Four-One.
We read you loud and clear.
变色龙的飞机正在视野内
Have the Chameleon aircraft in sight.
正在一万英尺高度尾随，朝南飞行
Am following at ten thousand feet, heading due south.
就是他，咬住尾巴。目前看来进展不错！
That's him. Right on the tail. So far so good!
都搞定了
All set.
有什么东西在跟着我们
Something's following us.
有另外一家飞机走同一路线？
Another airliner going the same way?
不，太小了
No, it's too small.
是架战斗机。给我雷达数据
It's a fighter. Give me a radar reading.
方位23-79​
Two-three decimal seven-nine.
Heslington, 战斗机偏离航线了！
Heslington, that fighter's off course!
盖特威克机场呼叫RAF-241，你可以听到吗？
Gatwick to RAF Two-Four-One. Do you read me?
那飞机可不是简单地偏离航线
That plane isn't just off course.
- 有事情发生了  - 你说得对，它失控了
- Something's happened to it.
- You're right. It's out of control.
盖特威克机场呼叫RAF-241，你可以听到吗？
Gatwick to RAF Two-Four-One. Do you read me?
我觉得你收不到回答了
I don't think you'll get a reply. //
信号变弱了，已经要从雷达上消失了
It's fading, dropping out of our radar.
Jean，给我接皇家空军，那家飞机坠毁了
Jean, get me RAF Manston. That plane's crashed.
看变色龙的飞机！肯定也出什么事了
Look at the Chameleon plane!
There's something wrong with that too.
唔
Hmmm?
它停止不动了！不可能啊
It's standing still! Impossible.
不，先生，光点是静止的
No sir, the blip's stationary.
这只意味着一件事情
That can only mean one thing...
它也坠毁了！
It's crashing too!
立即向飞行甲板汇报
Report to the flight deck immediately.
下一航班有多少人需要护照才能离开机场？
How many people require passports
in order to leave the airport on the next flight?
- 25个  - 这里你漏了一个
- Twenty-Five.  - You missed this one here.
对不起
I'm sorry.
继续吧
Carry on.
海上救援队报告说没有找到，先生
Negative report from Air Sea Rescue, sir.
但有两架飞机掉了，肯定会有残骸的痕迹啊
But with two aircraft ditching
there must be some signs of wreckage.
你为什么觉得变色龙的飞机是坠落到海里了？
Why do you think the Chameleon plane
crashed into the sea?
因为它从我们的雷达屏幕上消失了！
Because it disappeared off our radar screen!
但它一开始是静止没动！
But it stood still first!
因为它肯定是跟空军的飞机撞上了，然后掉落下去
Because it must have collided with
the RAF plane and dropped like a stone.
你为什么会这么想
Why do you think that?
要知道，当一架飞机像那样在雷达上静止不动
You see, when a plane on that radar
appears to stand still,
那么它事实上就是直线下落了
it is in point of fact dropping straight down.
- 直线上升怎么样？  - 噢，我亲爱的博士
- What about straight up?
- Oh my dear Doctor!
要能像那样跑出我们雷达的范围
To get above our radar umbrella like that
它必须垂直爬上达到100英里高
it'd have to climb vertically
until it was a hundred miles high.
那该死的高度就是外太空了
The darned thing would be in outer space.
正是这个！
Exactly!